let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following is not an OOPS concept?",
        answer: "C.Exception", // Correct answer
        options: [
          "A. Encapsulation",
"B. Polymorphism",
"C.Exception",
"D.Abstraction"
        ]
      }
      ,
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which feature of OOPS described the reusability of code",
    answer: "D.Inheritance",
    options: ["A.Abstraction", "B.Encapsulation", "C. Polymorphism", "D.Inheritance"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which among the following feature is not in the general definition of OOPS?",
    answer: "A.Duplicate or Redundant Data",
    options: [
      "A.Duplicate or Redundant Data",
      "B.Efficient Code",
      "C.Code reusability",

      "D.Modularity",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The memory that is allocated for any objects is ",
    answer: "D.RAM",
    options: [
      "A. Cache",
      "B. HDD",
      "C.ROM",
      "D.RAM",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: " A single program of OOPS contains _______ classes?",
    answer: "C.Any number",
    options: [
      "A. Only 1",
      "B.Only 999",
      "C.Any number",
      "D.Only 100",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
    answer: "D.All of the above",
    options: [
      "A. Variable",
      "B.Functions",
      "C.Objects",
      "D.All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",
    answer: "D.Division by zero",
   
    options: [
      "A.Syntax error",
      "B.Missing of semicolons",
      "C.Missing of Bracket",
      "D.Division by zero",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "  The 'function' and ' var' are known as:",
    answer: "C.Declaration statements",
  
    options: [
      "A. Keywords",
      "B.Data types",
      "C.Declaration statements",
      "D.Prototypes",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "  Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
    answer: "D.immediate if",
   
    options: [
      "A.Alternative to if-else",
      "B.Switch statement",
      "C.If-then-else statement",
      "D.immediate if",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
    answer: "B.Object-Based",
    
    options: [
      "A.Object-Oriented",
      "B.Object-Based",
      "C.Assembly-language",
      "D.High-level",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following is not a Java features?",
    answer: "C.Use of pointers",
    options: [
      "A.Dynamic",
      "B.Architecture Neutral",
      "C.Use of pointers",
      "D.Object-oriented",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "An interface with no fields or methods is known as a ______.",
    answer: "B.Marker Interface",
   
    options: [
      "A.Runnable Interface",
      "B.Marker Interface",
      "C.Abstract Interface",
      "D.CharSequence Interface",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: " In which memory a String is stored, when we create a string using new operator?",
    answer: "D.Heap memory",
  
    options: [
      "A. Stack",
      "B.tring memory",
      "C.Random storage space",
      "D.Heap memory",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which keyword is used for accessing the features of a package?",
    answer: "B.import",
   

    options: [
      "A.package",
      "B.import",
      "C.extends",
      "D.export",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "In java, jar stands for_____.",
    answer: "D.None of the above",
   
    options: [
      "A.Java Archive Runner",
      "B.Java Application Resource",
      "C.Java Application Runner",
      "D.None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: " The HTML attribute used to define the inline styles is ",
    answer: "A.style",
    

    options: [
      "A.style",
      "B.styles",
      "C.class",
      "D.None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to set the background image of an element?",
    answer: "B.background-image",

    options: [
      "A. background-attachment",
      "B.background-image",
      "C.background-color",
      "D.None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: " The CSS property used to make the text bold is -",
    answer: "A.font-weight : bold",
   

    options: [
      "A.font-weight : bold",
      "B.weight: bold",
      "C.weight: bold",
      "D.style: bold",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "The CSS property used to draw a line around the elements outside the border?",
    answer: "B.outline",
   

    options: [
      "A.border",
      "B.outline",
      "C.padding",
      "D.line",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The CSS property used to set the maximum width of the element's content box is -",
    answer: "A.max-width property",
    
    options: [
      "A.max-width property",
      "B.height property",
      "C.max-height property",
      "D.position property",
    ],
  },
];
